americannews.com 2016-02-07

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for americannews.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Your Access to and Control Over Information  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:

• See what data we have about you, if any.

• Change/correct any data we have about you.

• Have us delete any data we have about you.

• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

Security  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at americannewscontact@gmail.com .

UPDATE:

Third party vendors, including Google, and other ad networks use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. You can also check http://www.aboutads.info/ on how to opt out of third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising

To EU Users: Please read our disclosure notice as part of our compliance to the EU user consent policy:

We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. For more information on how Google uses data when you use our partner’ sites or apps, visit this link: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/

Reporting Copyright Violations  
Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) of 1998, 17 U.S.C. 512(c)(2), American News has a DMCA Registered Agent for notice of alleged DMCA copyright infringement. You may contact American News’ DMCA Registered Agent at email address mark@terryfirm.com or by mail to: Mark Terry, Esq., 801 Brickell Av. Suite 900, Miami, FL 33131. To file a notice of infringement with American News, the requirements specified in Title II of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 must be fulfilled. The text of this statute can be found at the United States Copyright Office website, located at http://www.copyright.gov. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us with this information:  
• A physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;  
• A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed upon;  
• A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the site;  
• Your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
• A statement by you that you have a good-faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;  
• A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.
